welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we'll quickly look at color and
我们将快速查看视频的颜色和
picking color choosing a certain color
挑选颜色选择特定的颜色
that we want to use in we'll look
我们想要用到的东西 我们会看看
at the different options we have for the
我们有不同的选择
color interface and different ways to
色彩界面和不同的方式
pick a color and then we will be using
选择一种颜色 然后我们将使用
color if you don't already have a blank
如果您还没有空白 请选择颜色
document you can just get one by going
文档你可以通过以下方式获得一份
to file new and then just leave
提交新文件 然后就离开
everything to default and hit OK and it
一切都是默认的 点击OK就可以了
brings up a nice blank square like this
像这样画出一个漂亮的空白正方形
so we have a nice square white canvas
所以我们有一块漂亮的正方形白色画布
one thing I will say is that we do not
我要说的一件事是 我们没有
have an alpha channel if we go over here
如果我们走到这里 会有一个Alpha通道
to the top right we can look and see we
在右上角我们可以看到我们
have a red green and a blue channel and
有一个红色的绿色和一个蓝色的通道
if we click on our layers we see we just
如果我们点击我们的层 我们就会看到
have one layer don't you don't need to
有一层 不是吗 你不需要
worry about any of this if it doesn't
如果它不能做到这一点 你就得担心
make any sense to you but just know that
对你来说有任何意义 但你要知道
we do not have transparency which is why
我们没有透明度 这就是为什么
if we go to our eraser and try and erase
如果我们拿起橡皮擦试着擦掉
this white we can't get to a transparent
这个白色我们不能得到一个透明的
background like we could if we had at a
背景就像我们在一个
alpha channel so for alpha channel if I
Alpha通道用于Alpha通道
right click and go add alpha Channel
右键单击并添加Alpha通道
now we could erase and these sort of
现在我们可以擦除这些东西
squares back here is transparency or
这里后面的方块是透明度或
like the Alpha Channel don't worry about
就像阿尔法频道一样 不用担心
that at all I'm gonna remove it right
我要把它取下来
now because we'll touch on that later in
现在 因为我们将在后面讨论这一点
the future but just know that's why
未来 但要知道这就是为什么
we're not gonna see options when we left
当我们离开时 我们看不到任何选择
click on our color to choose we can
点击我们的颜色 选择我们可以
choose a color but we're not gonna see
选择一种颜色 但我们不会看到
options for the Alpha channel or for
Alpha通道的选项或
transparency in here just yet anyway
不管怎样 这里的透明度还没有提高
okay so let's slow down a little bit and
好的 让我们慢一点 然后
go over here to choose our color we've
请到这里来选择我们的颜色
learned before if we start drawing if we
以前学过如果我们开始画画 如果我们
go back to select a black color we can
返回以选择我们可以选择的黑色
just draw with our brush or the pencil
只要用我们的画笔或铅笔画就行了
or lots of these different tools and we
或者许多这些不同的工具 我们
can draw in black to change the color we
可以用黑色来改变我们的颜色
just left-click on one of these two
只需左键单击这两个中的一个
squares either the white or the black
将白色或黑色方格
the one that's on top is the one we're
在上面的那个就是我们
using right now which is to black and we
现在使用的是黑人和我们
can select any shade of red in here we
在这里我们可以选择任何深浅不一的红色
can go in the top right hand corner is
可以走到右上角的是
pure red we can hit OK and now
纯红色 我们可以点击OK 现在
everything we draw will be in red we can
我们画的所有东西都会是红色的
come again and left-click and we can go
再来 左键点击 我们就可以走了
over and if we left click on hold we
结束 如果我们左键点击Hold We
kind of get these crosshairs and we can
有了这些靶子 我们就可以
see it's moving the dials around over
看 它正在把刻度盘移动到
here a little bit this might be
这里有一点 这可能是
different for you might be this LCH i
对你来说不同的可能是这个LCH I
have it selected on this
在这个上选择它
HSV and it's just changing different
HSV和它只是在改变不同
ways it's got a red green and a blue
它有红色、绿色和蓝色
channel we can also change the color
我们还可以更改频道的颜色
over here but I would recommend staying
在这里 但我建议你留下来
away from this when you're just starting
在你刚刚开始的时候远离这一切
out and only change your color over here
出去 只换一下你的颜色
on the left side portion so to change
在左侧部分 这样就可以改变了
the actual color we can select with left
我们可以使用Left选择的实际颜色
clicking we can go to our blues we can
点击我们可以进入我们的忧郁 我们可以
go to more like yellows or Red's we can
我们可以去更像黄色或红色的
left-click and hold and see how that
左键单击并按住 看看它如何
changes and when we get the the color or
变化 当我们得到颜色或
the hue that we want we can then select
然后我们可以选择我们想要的色调
mixing white with that or more blue and
把白色和那个或更多的蓝色混合在一起
under current it shows the color that
在当前状态下 它显示的颜色
we're currently on so we did have this
我们现在正在进行中 所以我们有这个
red color so it's the old and now we're
红色 所以它是旧的 现在我们是
going to be more of a blue and if we
会变得更蓝 如果我们
want to be more of a blue mixed with
想要更多地成为蓝色与
white we come up here and this is kind
白人 我们来到这里 这真是太好了
of a halfway between blue and white we
在蓝色和白色之间的中间地带
hit OK and we have sort of this blue
点击OK 我们就有这个蓝色的了
white color now another tool we haven't
白色现在是我们还没有的另一个工具
really looked at is the bucket filled
真的看起来是水桶满了
tool so maybe if I choose a different
所以如果我选择不同的工具
color like this green and we get a
像这样的绿色 我们就会得到一个
really pale green color hit OK we can go
真的是淡绿色 好的 我们可以走了
to the bucket fill tool or the what's it
到水桶填充工具 或者是什么
called fill tool yeah bucket fill tool
叫填充工具是的水桶填充工具
we left click on it and now we can click
我们左键点击它 现在我们可以点击
and it'll fill in everything within that
它会填满其中的所有东西
area will be that color so maybe we want
区域将是该颜色 所以也许我们想要
these eyes to be a purple color with
这双眼睛是紫色的
some black mixed in like a black purpley
一些黑色混杂在一起 就像黑色的紫色
we can select that color and go to okay
我们可以选择那个颜色 然后转到OK
and we can fill in these eyes now so it
我们现在可以填满这些眼睛 所以它
fills in the whole area so now we've
填充了整个区域 所以现在我们已经
drawn a little face right here there's a
画了一张小脸就在这里有一个
toggle too if we want so if we grab the
如果我们想的话也可以切换 如果我们抓住
eraser tool right now and we start to
橡皮擦工具 现在我们开始
erase it's going to erase this back this
擦掉它会把这个擦回去
color here so not the purple you erase
在这里涂上颜色 而不是你擦掉的紫色
this cover that's behind which is a
后面的这个封面是一个
white square right now so if we erase
现在是白色方块 所以如果我们擦掉
everything is erasing in white but it
一切都在白色中抹去 但它
doesn't have to be that way we can
不一定非得这样我们才能
change the erase color by clicking on
通过单击更改擦除颜色
that one and change it to a different
并将其更改为不同的
color as well maybe we change it to a
颜色也可以 也许我们可以把它改成
shade of red and it okay so now when we
红色的阴影和它的好所以现在当我们
erase it'll be this shade of darker you
抹去它将会是你的深色
know maroon red color and we can toggle
知道栗红的颜色 我们可以切换
between the two if we click this button
在这两者之间 如果我们点击这个按钮
now the foreground color is this sort of
现在前景色是这样一种
maroon and the background color or the
栗色和背景颜色或
color of our erase tool will be this
我们的擦除工具的颜色是这样的
purple this darker purple
紫色这是深紫色
when we have our drawing tool selected
当我们选择了绘图工具时
like the brush we can do that too we can
像刷子一样 我们也可以做到这一点
draw let's change the color of this to
让我们将这个的颜色更改为
more of a open somes in contrasting more
更多的是开放的一些在对比更多
of a green so now we have a green right
所以现在我们有了绿色的权利
here and if we want to just toggle
在这里 如果我们想要切换
between the two we can left-click and
在这两者之间 我们可以左键单击并
now we have the purple so play with that
现在我们有了紫色 那就来玩吧
toggling between the two it's also X is
在这两者之间切换也是X是
the shortcut key if you hover over it
将鼠标悬停在快捷键上
tells you press X and you can toggle see
告诉您按下X 您可以切换(请参阅
we can draw a line press X and keep
我们可以画一条线 按下X并保持
toggling between those two by pressing X
通过按X键在这两个之间切换
on our keyboard monster on my keyboard
我们的键盘怪物在我的键盘上
shortcuts real quick so X will toggle
快捷键非常快 这样X就会切换
that okay let's go back into the colors
好的 让我们回到颜色上来
now so I want to show you some different
现在我想向你们展示一些不同的
options we have so we've just looked at
我们有多种选择 所以我们刚刚了解了
this one right here if we hover over
如果我们在这里悬停的话就是这个
this is what's called the the color
这就是所谓的颜色
selector if we right click we see what
选择器如果我们右击 我们会看到什么
they all are we have CMYK we have
他们都是我们有CMYK我们有
water color we have wheel and we have
水彩 我们有轮子 我们有
palette and that's right clicking to get
调色板 点击鼠标右键即可
to those options or we can click these
这些选项 或者我们可以点击这些
tiny little icons once you get familiar
一旦你熟悉了 就会有小小的图标
with them you can just click on them so
使用它们 您只需点击它们即可
CMYK is cyan magenta yellow and K is the
CMYK是青洋红黄色 K是
black color so you can choose your color
黑色 这样你就可以选择你的颜色
this way you can choose this is done in
这样 您可以选择在中完成此操作
printing a lot you can choose by mixing
打印很多你可以通过混合选择的东西
these different colors and you create a
这些不同的颜色 您创建了一个
color so we've created this sort of
所以我们创造了这种颜色
orange color and again as we move these
橙色 当我们移动这些东西时
it's changing the dials over here under
它正在改变这里下面的刻度盘
the red green blue and the hue
红色、绿色、蓝色和色调
saturation and value is what this HSB
饱和度和价值是这个HSB
stands for so we can choose our color
代表我们可以选择我们的颜色
this way and we can hit OK and now we've
这样我们就可以点击OK 现在我们已经
got a nice color for printing that a
我买了一种很适合打印的颜色
printer can interpret it knows how to
打印机可以解释它知道如何
make this ugly brownish color and if we
把这个难看的棕色做出来 如果我们
add more cyan which is like a bluish
添加更多青色 就像蓝色
color and take out the magenta which is
涂上颜色 拿出洋红 这是
more like a red and take out the yellow
更像是红色 去掉黄色
we're gonna get just cyan so this is
我们只会得到青色 所以这是
just a cyan color now okay let's go back
现在就是青色 好的 我们回去吧
and see what else we have we have this
看看我们还有什么 我们有这个
watercolor and watercolors one I'm
水彩画和水彩画合二为一
actually not quite sure if it's working
实际上不太确定它是否起作用了
correctly in this version but it's one
在这个版本中是正确的 但它是一个
that I don't use anyway you can select
我不会用的 你可以选择
colors in watercolor but one that I do
水彩画 但我只画一幅
use a lot is this color wheel this next
用得多的是这个色轮这个下边
one the color wheel that you choose
一个你选择的色轮
between white in one
白与白合二为一
corner black in the other corner and
另一个角落里的黑色角落和
then full color saturation in that other
然后在另一个中使用全色饱和度
corner and you can mix between any of
角落和你可以混合在任何
those colors to create a nice color and
这些颜色创造出一种漂亮的颜色
then if you want to change the hue of
然后 如果您想更改色调
the color you come around and you can
你周围的颜色 你可以
left-click in this circle to find a nice
在此圆圈中左键单击以找到一个不错的
hue and then a mix between either white
色调 然后是白色或白色之间的混合
and black or white and that color or
黑色或白色 而那颜色或
black in that color so this is a good a
黑色是那种颜色 所以这是一个很好的
good way to pick colors as well you can
挑选颜色的好方法你也可以
pick the same colors in this in all
在这件衣服里选一样的颜色
different methods you can pick the same
不同的方法你可以选择相同的方法
colors it's just a different interface
颜色只是一个不同的界面
for how you want to pick the last thing
你想要怎样挑选最后一件东西
we have here is our palette so this is
这是我们的调色板 所以这是
the colors that we've used in the past
我们过去用过的颜色
if you want to quickly jump back to that
如果你想迅速回到那个问题上
ugly brown color we can do that or this
难看的棕色 我们可以做那个或这个
kind of this magenta color we had picked
有点像我们选的洋红颜色
earlier or some of these lighter green
早些时候或一些浅绿色的
so it keeps a history of the palette
因此它保留了调色板的历史记录
you're using so you can jump back and
你正在使用 这样你就可以跳回
forth between certain colors one last
在某些颜色之间向前移动最后一次
thing I want to talk about is if we do
我想谈的是如果我们这么做了
change over here if we want to change
如果我们想换衣服 就在这里换
the value of the red green and blue you
红绿蓝你的价值
can toggle between 0 and 100 showing
可以在0和100之间切换显示
that or 0 and 255 a lot of times if
或者是0和255很多次 如果
you're working with color especially in
你在处理颜色 特别是在
like HTML or different in like websites
类似于Html或类似网站中的不同
and things you might want to have a
以及你可能想要的东西
value between 0 and 255 so in that case
介于0和255之间的值 因此在这种情况下
when you do maximum red it's 255 and
当你做最大红色时 它是255
minimum is 0 but some people don't work
最小值为0 但有些人不工作
in web or maybe especially if you're
在网络上 或者特别是如果你是
working in like CMYK and light color you
像CMYK和浅色你一样工作
maybe want to do between 0 and 100 it's
可能想要在0到100之间
just personal preference but then that
只是个人喜好 但后来
way when you turn up red to the full
当你完全变红的时候
amount it's 100% and so you know 50 is
金额是100% 所以你知道50是
50% it kind of helps you understand if
50%它可以帮助你理解
you have 25% of a certain color or not
你有没有25%的某种颜色
anyway that's kind of the different
无论如何 那是一种不同的
toggles we have there one last thing
切换我们还有最后一件事
I'll show you is we can select this here
我向你展示的是我们可以在这里选择这个
which is the eyedropper tool so we can
这就是吸管工具 所以我们可以
pick a certain color from our image like
从我们的图像中选择某种颜色 如
this black and then we can choose that
这个是黑色的 然后我们可以选择那个
color or we can pick this purple color
颜色或者我们可以选这个紫色
that we had before this is especially
在此之前我们所拥有的特别是
useful if you have an actual image
如果您有实际的图像 则很有用
brought in that you're working on like a
带来了你正在做的就像一个
photograph you can pick a certain pixel
你可以选择某一像素的照片
color from that image and know exactly
从图像中提取颜色并准确地知道
what that
那是什么？
is and be able to use it as well so
是并且能够使用它 所以
hopefully that's made a little bit of
希望这能让你有一点
sense go ahead and play with this the
理智 继续玩这个游戏
color different color options we have
颜色我们有不同的颜色选择
here I will say there's also a color
在这里 我会说还有一种颜色
picker tool as well right here if we
选取器工具也在这里 如果我们
hover over we can pick a color this way
悬停在上面 我们可以用这种方式挑选颜色
as well and just start using that color
开始使用这种颜色
so now we have this red we can click on
现在我们有了这个红色的我们可以点击
the color picker and we can pick this
颜色选择器 我们可以选择这个
blue color and then we can draw in that
然后我们就可以画出
as well
以及
so that's another way to pick colors
所以这是另一种选择颜色的方法
from the image you're working with well
从你的形象来看
I'm gonna leave this video here go ahead
我把这段录像留在这里继续
and leave questions or comments below if
并在下面留下问题或评论
you have any and I'll catch you in the
你有任何 我会赶上你在
next video
下一个视频